Miss Christmas is a tv movie, romance, drama film directed by Mike Rohl.
Holly Khun, known to Chicago as “Miss Christmas,” always finds a beautiful tree for the
plaza, but this year’s was damaged, and the lighting ceremony is in 10 days.
Hoping for a miracle, she combs through fan mail, and finds Joey
McNary of Klaus, Wisconsin, has the perfect tree.
Off she goes to Klaus, where she meets Joey’s handsome dad Sam.
Holly, played by Brooke D'Orsay.
Sam, played by Marc Blucas.
Joey, played by Luke Roessler.
Aimee, played by Erin Boyes.
Erin, played by Fiona Vroom.
Neighbor, played by James Rha.
The Father Christmas film series is an American/Canadian trilogy, starring Erin
Krakow and Niall Matter, based on the novels of Robin Jones Gunn.
The films were originally broadcast in the USA on Hallmark Movies & Mysteries, as
part of the channels' "Miracles of Christmas" seasonal programming.
The films follow the story of Miranda Chester (Krakow), as she visits the cozy sundown
town of Carlton Heath, Vermont, in search of the truth about her parentage.
While there she meets, and falls in love with local
lawyer/hotelier Ian McKendrick (Matter).
The tone is emotional.